<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Momma</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_item_list">Items</string>
    <string name="title_item_detail">Item Detail</string>
    <string name="title_activity_scrolling">Qualities of Shia</string>
    <string name="title_favorite_places">Our Places</string>
    <string name="large_text">
        "My Love....\n\n"

        "Your trust is the most basic foundation of our true love."
        "Loyalty in our relationships not only brings emotional stability but also increases intimacy levels, what I learned from you."
        "Your timely support help me to settle. If you were not there, I would not be able to what I have achieved in my life.\n"
        "You take care of my feelings just like yours and I really express my gratitude towards you for the same. "
        "I really love for Self confidence. Its really invaluable and means everything for dealing with adversity, such as dealing with family members,
        friends, the pressure in college and the tough time. "
        "I have never met any other person with the same kind hearted and strength you have. "
        "\n"
        "You will achieve a lot in life my love and I know that the upcoming challenge will not pull you down. "
        "You will show your beauty and strength to the world and get the results that will convince you. "
        "\n\n"

        "Always Remember that n\n"

        "I am always here for you and will never let you down, I am praying for you my love. "
        "And one more think, I appreciate your work in fitness. You have done a great job. Love the way you have done...\n\n"

    </string>
    <string name="title_activity_login">Momma</string>

    <!-- Strings related to login -->
    <string name="prompt_email">Email</string>
    <string name="prompt_password">Password</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in">You know the credentials</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in_short">Sign in</string>
    <string name="error_invalid_email">This email address is invalid my love</string>
    <string name="error_invalid_password">This password is too short my love</string>
    <string name="error_incorrect_password">This password is incorrect my love</string>
    <string name="error_field_required">This field is required</string>
    <string name="permission_rationale">"Contacts permissions are needed for providing email
        completions."
    </string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="title_activity_maps">Map</string>
    <string name="quote_one">I was the one you always dreamed of,
    You were the one I tried to draw
        How dare you say it's nothing to me?
        Baby, you're the only light I ever saw
    </string>

    <string name="quote_two">Where There is a Charity and Wisdom, There is Neither fear nor Ignorance.</string>
    <string name="quote_three">If At First You Dont Succeed.
        Fixed Your PONYTAIL and Try Again.
    </string>
    <string name="quote_four">Sometimes I look at you and I wonder How I got to Be So Damn Lucky.</string>
    <string name="quote_five">I dont think You Understand How IMPORTANT Its for me to Hear the Sound of Your Voice Everyday.</string>
    <string name="quote_six">You are not just another person, you are the love of my life.</string>
    <string name="quote_seven">When you really Care About Someone, Their Mistakes Never change our Feelings Because The Minds Get Angry but The Heart that Still Cares. </string>
    <string name="quote_eight">Strength and Beauty must go Hand in Hand. </string>
    <string name="quote_nine">Rock with Rocky!!! </string>
</resources>
